#### Contact

marilyn.schwartzbeck@hcahea lthcare.com

www.linkedin.com/in/schwartzbeck-marilyn-87ba0889 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Clinical Research
Healthcare Information Technology
Healthcare Management

# Schwartzbeck Marilyn

Staff Nurse /Assistant Nurse Manager at Bayshore Medical Center HCA Healthcare

Pasadena, Texas

### Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Customer Service, Microsoft Word, Patient Safety, and Healthcare Information Technology (HIT). Strong healthcare services professional graduated from Hutchinson Hospital School of Nursing.

### Experience

HCA Healthcare Staff Nurse March 2007 - Present (13 years 3 months) Houston, Texas Area

PACU Assistant Nurse Manager for 7 years until 10/2017. Currently relief ANM and FT staff nurse. Managed the PACU unit patient flow, patient assignments, staff schedule. Provide nursing care of all acuity levels of post anesthesia patient care within ASPAN standards of care. Proficient in Meditech/ CPOE. Committees: Nurse Staffing Effectiveness; Professional Growth & Development.

Bayshore Medical Center
14 years 4 months

RN-PACU
February 2006 - Present (14 years 4 months)

RN Assistant Nurse Manager February 2006 - Present (14 years 4 months) PACU

## Education

Capella University
BSN (April 2019), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse

Hutchinson Hospital School of Nursing Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse